ANURADHA PATHAK

NETWORK SUPPORT ENGINEER



CONTACTS



+919399892581



anuradhapathak 88@gmail.com



Gurugram

LINKS

LinkedIn:
https://www.linkedin.co
m/in/anuradha-
pathak19/

SKILLS

- Routing: BGP, OSPF, EIGRP, RIP, RIPv2
- Switching: VLAN, DTP, VTP, STP, RSTP, EtherChannel
- Security: ACLs, Port Security, RADIUS, TACACS+
- WAN: VPN IPsec, GRE, DMVPN
- NAT
- HSRP
- SNMP, TELNET, SSH, DHCP, DNS

ABOUT ME

Seeking a challenging career opportunity in Information technology as a Network Engineer in related roles.

Having experience of 4 years & 7 months in Telecom and Networking domain. Having experience of 3 years & 9 months as a Support Engineer with expertise in CCNA – Routing & Switching.

WORK EXPERIENCE

InKnowTech Pvt. Ltd.

Gurugram Oct 2019 – Aug 2020

Network Support Engineer

Project - Accenture-Bharati Airtel, Manesar

- The project involved Airtel, which as an ISP, provides WAN internet connectivity to its customers and Accenture, which as a partner, supports Airtel's infrastructure by providing technical expertise, troubleshooting and resolutions at Layers 1 to 3 of network architecture.
- Took ownership of service Requests (SRs).
- Troubleshooting of P2P, lease line, MPLS network link.
- Telnet of MPLS Provider Edge router by using putty and RD session.
- Provided end to end resolutions within 4 hours of SLA Report with region for outage (RFO).
- Verified duplex matching, Rf configuration of Radwin, Makset, Cembium RF device via RF NMS.
- Data gathering via tools such as Metasolve (M6), B2B, ITNM, TAC Asist.

Aspire Broadband

Singrauli Sep 2018 – Mar 2019

Technical Support Engineer

Project – Hardware / Support

- Troubleshooting: MIKROTIK R260GSP, MIKROTIK SXT Lite5, DSL Routers - TENDA/ SYROTECH/ BINATONE, REVO-ONU
- Network monitoring of company as well client via dude.
- Bandwidth monitoring in CCR in Win box.

SOFT SKILLS

- Ability to rapidly build relationships
- Interested in gaining practical knowledge
- Willingness to learn new technologies
- Comprehensive problem-solving abilities.

LANGUAGES

- Hindi
- English

CERTIFICATIONS

- CCNA(R&S) ID -CISCO13482667
- Pursuing CCNP(R&S)
- SD-WAN self-trained
- Linux self-trained
- Palo Alto ongoing self-training

- Configuring DSL routers and implementing solutions remote access via Any desk software.
- Troubleshooting traffic and outage related issues
- Generating tickets and sending RFO reports to clients.
- Reporting of technicians (working under) and assign tickets via bell-Radius.
- Client follow-ups, making Quotations and Create
- Troubleshooting outage-fiber-cut via OTDR devices.
- Crimping and patching LAN cable via crimping tools and fiber cable splicing machine.

7 Layer Technologies

Lucknow

Apr 2016 – Aug 2018

Technical Support Engineer

- Responsible to resolve all technical issues for
- Cisco IOS installation, backup, restore, reboot devices, files TFTP server.

Reliance

Communications

Singrauli

Jun 2015 – Mar 2016

MIS

Responsible for customer's SIM activation endto-end process and resolved technical issues with respect to activation.

EDUCATION

RGPV

Bhopal

2014

Bachelor of Engineering

Electronics and Communication

RGPV

Bhopal

2010

Diploma

Electronics and Telecommunication

SSB

Singrauli

2005

Secondary Certificate

General science